YURIY KOSHYK

With almost 5 years of experience, I combine design and technical expertise to create impactful digital experiences focusing on business and user needs. As a generalist in multiple domains, I always try to find the right unique approach for every specific case. Outside of work, I enjoy movies, books, playing basketball, and doing street photography.

Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg, DE

yuriykoshyk.com linkedin.com/in/yuriy-koshyk yuriy.koshyk@gmail.com +380974399377

WORK HISTORY

PRODUCT DESIGNER

KOSH | Mar 2020 - Present

- Delivered 15+ projects, focusing on UX/UI design to drive business growth and user satisfaction;
- · Led full design research cycles, including user research, prototyping, and usability testing;
- · Translated business requirements and market insights into innovative design solutions;
- · Created high-performance digital products aligned with business metrics;
- · Monitored KPIs to optimise designs based on user feedback and data-driven insights.

HEAD OF SYSTEMS & IT (CTO)

DF Druckluft-Fachhandel GmbH | Aug 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Led the tech side of a multi-million dollar e-commerce company;
- Increased company revenue by 10% in first months with optimization of UX and system processes;
- · Effectively managed internal cross-functional team + 4 external partner companies;
- · Implemented the Agile methodology in the majority of the departments;
- · Successfully completed the company migration to Atlas Copco Group.

UX/UI DESIGNER & FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Heimdal Data ApS | Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

- · Adhered to design standards and collaborate with stakeholders;
- · Developed user-friendly interfaces with a focus on user experience;
- · Wrote clean and scalable code that increased product performance;
- · Conduct user research and gather requirements for the design process;
- · Brought creative design trends and new technologies to the company's projects.

PRINCIPLES

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Design Systems

Prototyping

Material Design

Human-Centered Design

Heuristic evaluation

Product Thinking

Usability Testing & A/B Testing

User Research

TOOLS

Figma, ProtoPie, Hotjar

Adobe Creative Suite, Blender

Google Analytics, PowerBI, SQL

HTML5, CSS3, SASS

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js

GSAP, Famer Motion, Tailwind

Webflow, Framer

AWARDS

Best Innovation and Creativity
Big Pitch Competition

EDUCATION

PR) TR

UX Design Medium Projector Institute



Frontend Developer
IT School GolT



Media Communications Diploma

Bournemouth University International College



Humber College
Foundation in Computing

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

EVENTPOS [Figma, Adobe Creative Suite]

Role: Product Designer

Mobile payment solution specifically designed for events.

<u>DF DRUCKLUFT-FACHHANDEL</u> [Agile, Azure, PowerBI, HTML, SASS, JS, SQL, Figma, Adobe CS]

Role: Head of Systems & IT

Multi-million dollar e-commerce leader for complete compressed air solutions (a part of Atlas Copco Group).